

OLKOV MARK

Date of birth:02.03.1995

City: Kraków

Phone: +34627978437

EMAIL: olkovmark@gmail.com

BRIEF INFORMATION

I work in the technical field. Quickly understand any software or device.

Experience in Java Kotlin C# React JavaScript

Experience working with clients and objects. Understanding digital devices

The solution is necessary for urgent tasks already in ready-made projects (Java, Kotlin, Angular, React, Express; JavaScript)

EXPERIENCE

E-life
(Medical Information
System)
Implementation Team
Leader

05/2020-наст.время

I set up software for hospitals, traveled around the country to train specialists to work with the program. Analyzed requests for new functionality, introduced new functionality. He was engaged in the development of a program for connecting laboratory analyzers to the system (Java), connected analyzers to the system at the facility. Worked with MSSQL database. Creation of a commercial WEB application for doctors(Angular)

Biosol (Biometric protection) Technician

07/2019-03/2020

Understood the principle of operation of devices and software on biometric protection, created a wiring diagram on the site, connected and configured In parallel, he created Software for Android for a call center with streaming video (Java)

LG Electronics B2B ID Engineer 07/2018 - 07/2019 I met with partners and customers, trained the technical part, set up the equipment at the facility, found the best option for the customer.

Freelance Unity3D Developer 06/2016 - 07/2018

He was engaged in the development of mobile games for Android to order from scratch on the Unity3D platform (C#)

TV channel MCP "Dni-Pro"

Director-Montage, Operator

06/2014 - 06/2016

He was engaged in shooting material and editing videos. Worked on news, author's works and commercials

EDUCATION

NAU 2012 - 2016

Institute of Computer Information Technologies, Computer Engineering

PURPOSE

I am looking for versatile work in interesting projects for self-development and getting good experience in which it is necessary not just to work, but to solve certain problems.